All India, we have been hearing since childhood that
who has seen tomorrow, this is the first time I am feeling it, I had
thought that I will have to think before leaving the house, it will be
difficult to hug,
welcome guests, right after learning
knowledge-science, the faces of superheroes change,
I had thought at this time that
rockstars will emerge from there,
my grandparents, we will learn internet and doodle on cooking,
we will click on the pictures of our loved ones, we will
value our life so much that we will not
see tomorrow tomorrow but from today, when things become priceless, we do
not take any chances, it has happened, this is
MP3,
hence ICICI Prudential Life
Kraft Smart All in One Temple Run, we will see tomorrow or
today